okay let me at least let me get started
好吧，至少让我开始
anyway and if they have to make
无论如何，如果他们必须
adjustments they'll make adjustments the
调整，他们将进行调整
title of this is parallel streams
标题是并行流
completable futures and all that the
可完备的期货及所有
idea is to look at the concurrence
想法是看并发
mechanisms and parallel mechanisms
机制和并行机制
inside of Java
Java内部
now I specifically was referring to Java
现在我专门指的是Java
eight of course everything carries over
八，当然一切都会延续
right to Java nine they've added a few
Java 9的权利，他们增加了一些
methods to the API in Java nine but
Java中API的方法九但
basically it's the same exact stuff so
基本上是一样的东西，所以
anything I'm going to talk about now is
我现在要谈论的是
applicable to both a 10-9 in fact I have
既适用于10-9，也适用于
run this code the code I'm going to show
运行此代码，我将显示的代码
you is works under both Java eight and
您在Java 8和Java下都可以工作
Java nine and I'll give you the
Java 9，我给你
information for that now my name is Ken
信息，现在我叫肯
cousin by the way it's cousin like the
表哥，就像
relative even though it doesn't look
亲戚，即使它看起来不
like it we think it's a Ellis Island job
喜欢它，我们认为这是埃利斯岛的工作
or something my company's cousin IT I
或我公司的表亲IT
call it cousin I T my wife refers to it
堂兄IT称呼它，我的妻子指的是它
as cousin it like the Adams family it
作为表亲，就像亚当斯一家一样
was her idea
是她的主意
what can you do any rate there's my
你能做什么呢？
email address website blog and Twitter
电子邮件地址网站博客和Twitter
handle feel free to contact me whenever
请随时与我联系
my delete key works as well as anybody's
我的删除密钥与任何人的都一样有效
right any rate a few years ago I wrote a
好吧，几年前我写了一篇
book called making job a groovy that's a
这本书叫把工作变成时髦
Java groovy integration book published
Java Groovy集成书出版
through Manning last year I wrote a book
去年通过曼宁我写了一本书
called Gradle recipes for Android just
被称为Android的Gradle食谱
to undercut sales entirely if you were
如果您是
to go to Gradle dot org and register you
去Gradle dot org并注册你
can get that book for free if you want
可以免费得到那本书
so shows my negotiating capabilities I
这样显示了我的谈判能力
negotiated a royalty on a book that I
我就一本书商定了版税
knew they were going to give away so you
知道他们会放弃，所以你
don't want me negotiating your next
不想让我跟你谈判
contract this is the book that I have
合同这是我拥有的书
out now
现在出来
modern Java recipes and everything I'm
现代Java食谱以及我所拥有的一切
going to talk to you about pretty much
要和你谈很多
is in this book we are actually having a
在这本书中，我们实际上有一个
book signing at O'Reilly in the
在O'Reilly签署书
exhibitor I think they're one one floor
参展商我认为它们是一层楼
down over by the wall tomorrow at
明天在墙下
afternoon at two o'clock if you're
如果你在下午两点
interested now the reason I bring it up
现在有兴趣我提出来的原因
is partly because my editor be really
部分原因是我的编辑确实
annoyed if I didn't but also because
如果我不生气，那也是因为
these are the URLs for the github
这些是github的URL
repositories for the code I'm going to
我要去的代码库
show you the entire book repository is
向您展示整个图书库
under github calm
在github下平静
my last name and then the name is Java
我的姓氏，然后是Java
underscore 8 underscore recipes now I
下划线现在我有8个下划线食谱
have several small examples I'm going to
我有几个小例子
show you out of there
带你去那里
but then I needed a larger example to
但是我需要一个更大的例子
show how the completable future stuff is
展示如何完成未来的工作
put together I threw in a parallel
放在一起我平行
stream as well that one is under a
流，也有人在
separate repo called CF box scores I'm
我称为CF盒分数的单独回购
going to download box score data from
要从中下载盒分数数据
Major League Baseball online so I'm I'm
美国职棒大联盟线上，所以我
probably asking a lot out of our Wi-Fi
可能对我们的Wi-Fi提出了很多要求
but hey you know if you don't you don't
但嘿，你知道你是否不知道
try you know let's see what happens
尝试知道让我们看看会发生什么
right if it was easy anybody can do it
对，如果这很容易，任何人都可以做到
so at any rate I have two github repos
所以无论如何我有两个github仓库
involved and you're welcome to take
参与其中，欢迎您参加
anything you like out of there for the
您想要的任何东西
book I also have a repo called Java
这本书我也有一个叫做Java的仓库
underscore 9 underscore recipes for the
下划线的9下划线食谱
handful of Java 9 ones as well but I'm
少数几个Java 9，但我
not using that for this talk if you have
如果您有这个话，请不要使用它
a safari account I have a whole bunch of
一个野生动物园帐户，我有一堆
video courses at Safari Books online I
Safari图书在线上的视频课程I
also teach training classes there and of
还在那里教训练课程
course all the books are available there
当然所有的书都在那里
as well but that's more self marketing
也是，这更多是自我营销
than I could stomach so let's move on
比我能忍受的多，所以让我们继续前进
now yeah let's get this out of the way
现在是的，让我们摆脱它
because anytime you talk about
因为任何时候你谈论
concurrency and parallelism somebody
并发和并行性
gets annoyed and they get very precise
变得烦恼，他们变得非常精确
about it I'm defining it this way this
关于它，我这样定义它
is how I understand it currency is
我是如何理解货币的
something you design for you're talking
您正在为自己设计的内容
about having multiple things that can
关于拥有多个可以
run at the same time that can go
可以同时运行
concurrently as they say but that
正如他们所说的那样，但是
doesn't mean they are running
并不代表他们在跑步
concurrently it just means we try to
同时意味着我们试图
design them with that in mind
设计时要牢记这一点
whereas parallelism is when we actually
而并行性是当我们实际上
are running two things at the same time
同时运行两件事
so in principle you have to have
所以原则上你必须有
multiple cores to do parallelism
多核做并行
although I would argue if you do
虽然我会争论你是否愿意
multiple threads it's effectively
多线程有效
parallel as well but that's the gray
平行，但这就是灰色
area that's where a lot of debates will
将会有很多辩论的领域
happen I'm going to try to use those
碰巧我要尝试使用那些
words with that in mind those are the
记住这些话是
definitions you tend to see online so I
您倾向于在网上看到的定义，所以我
thought I'd bring them here so alright
以为我会把它们带到这里好
there's the definitions now I want to
现在我要定义
bring up something that you may be aware
提出一些你可能知道的东西
of a rich Hickey the creator of the
富有的Hickey的创造者
closure programming language closure
闭包编程语言闭包
with a.j basically Lisp on the JVM gave
与基本上在JVM上的Lisp给
a keynote presentation several years ago
几年前的主题演讲
at the conference called strange loops
在会议上被称为怪圈
some of you may know it and st. Louis
你们当中有些人可能知道路易
it's called simple made easy now it's a
它被称为简单变得容易，现在
fascinating keynote but it's you
引人入胜的主题演讲，但只有你
from my point of view for one reason the
从我的角度来看，出于一个原因
concept was as some things are
概念是一些东西
inherently simple meaning conceptually
概念上固有的简单含义
simple and even simple and execution you
简单甚至简单执行
know exactly what to do step by step
确切地知道该怎么做一步一步
whereas the concept of easy is that hey
而easy的概念是
it's a method call in a library and
这是库中的方法调用，
there could be a ton of complexity under
下可能会有大量的复杂性
the hood but it was easy to do with the
引擎盖，但很容易做到
parallel streams in Java eight they have
Java 8中的并行流
made it very easy to experiment with
使实验变得非常容易
parallelism but that doesn't mean that
并行性，但这并不意味着
getting excellent performance out of
从中获得出色的性能
concurrent parallel applications is
并发并行应用程序是
simple see it's it can be very complex
简单看，这可能非常复杂
and I'll talk about what the general
我将谈论一般
generally accepted requirements are for
一般接受的要求是
this to be beneficial for this to work
这对它的工作很有好处
out but I don't want to pretend that
出来，但我不想假装
even though they've added a lot of
即使他们添加了很多
classes to make it easy to experiment
方便实验的课程
it's still not a simple phenomenon going
这仍然不是一个简单的现象
to parallel stuff here I want to combine
平行的东西在这里我想结合
that notion by the way that's one of my
那个想法是我的一种
favorite demonstrations or illustrations
最喜欢的示范或插图
of the word easy is that I remember
容易这个词的意思是我记得
there was a script presented for Star
曾为Star呈现过剧本
Trek The Next Generation having an
跋涉着下一代
anniversary this year and they the
今年的周年纪念日，他们
writer had written out this elaborate
作家已经写出了这个精心制作的
set of instructions for Captain Picard
皮卡德船长的指令集
to tell him how to go into orbit around
告诉他如何进入轨道
a planet and he crossed it all out and
一个星球，他把它全部划掉了，
when standard orbit ensign and that was
当标准轨道少尉，那是
it so that's easy without necessarily
它很容易，没有必要
being simple and that's the kind of idea
很简单，这就是这种想法
I'm looking for now I also want to
我现在正在寻找，我也想
mention a comment from Brian gets I'm
提到Brian的评论让我成为
sure you're familiar with Brian gets if
确定您熟悉Brian，如果
he's in this room please don't tell me
他在这个房间里，请不要告诉我
I'll be far too intimidated to complete
我实在太吓人了，无法完成
this talk ok Brian gets is the author of
好的谈话，布莱恩得到的是
Java concurrency in practice he also has
在实践中他也有Java并发
was one of the chief architects for java
是Java的首席设计师之一
at son and now oracle you know one of
在儿子和现在的甲骨文你知道其中之一
the real Giants in the in the industry
业内真正的巨人
when he talks about concurrency actually
当他谈论并发时
when he talks about anything I listen I
当他谈论任何事情时，我在听
don't generally understand but I do
通常不了解，但我知道
listen he has said many times that
听他说过很多次
parallelism is strictly an optimization
并行严格来说是一种优化
this is coming most recently out of one
这是最近发生的一个
of a series of articles he wrote on Java
他在Java上写的一系列文章
streams at developerworks the IBM site
在developerWorks IBM网站上流
developerworks
开发人员
put in a link there to our article four
在此处链接到第四条
out of a series of five that's the one
在五个系列中，只有一个
where he talks about parallel streams
他谈论并行流
you're welcome to all of this of course
当然欢迎您
the presentations been uploaded but if
演示文稿已上传，但如果
you need it before that just contact me
在联系我之前，您需要它
I'll be happy to send it to you any rate
我很乐意将其发送给您
so the idea with all the parallelism and
这样的想法与所有并行性和
concurrency mechanisms in Java is to get
Java中的并发机制是为了
your code working sequentially first
您的代码首先按顺序工作
work with a sequential stream and then
使用顺序流，然后
once that's working then you can
一旦工作，那么您可以
experiment with parallelism and have
试验并行性并具有
some confidence that you can draw some
有信心，你可以画一些
conclusions and get some benefits out of
结论并从中获得一些好处
it all right
没关系
that's all the waivers let's go on these
这就是所有的豁免，让我们继续
are all the factory methods if you will
是所有工厂方法吗
the mechanisms that we use in Java to
我们在Java中使用的机制
create streams there's the stream method
创建流有stream方法
that's a default method that's been
这是一个默认的方法
added to collection there is the of
添加到集合中的是
method the factory method that's used in
method用于的工厂方法
many classes in Java eight to produce an
Java 8中的许多类产生一个
object
宾语
there's the iterate method that takes a
有一个迭代方法需要一个
seed and then a unary operator and
种子，然后是一元运算符，
provides successive values by applying
通过应用提供连续值
the unary operator over and over again
一元运算符一遍又一遍
to the existing values and then there's
到现有的价值，然后有
the generate method that takes a
生成方法需要一个
supplier it just invokes the supplier
供应商，它只是调用供应商
over and over again
一遍又一遍地
retrieving results as we go all of those
当我们进行所有这些操作时检索结果
by default produce sequential streams so
默认情况下会产生顺序流
whenever you if you don't let's put it
每当你不放的时候
this way if you don't specifically say
这样如果你不特别说
parallel it's sequential that's the idea
并行是顺序的
now there are a couple ways to make a
现在有几种方法可以使
parallel stream one is that collection
并行流之一是那个集合
also has a parallel stream method so
也有并行流方法
that we have that option as well and
我们也有选择
oftentimes what I'll do is I'll create
我经常要做的就是创造
an app with a stream in it and then just
一个带有流的应用程序，然后
change it to parallel stream to see if
将其更改为并行流以查看是否
that improves anything or what I have to
可以改善我所需要的一切
tweak in order to get benefit out of
调整以便从中受益
that there's also a method called
还有一种方法叫做
parallel in-stream now technically
现在从技术上讲并行流内
that's in base stream the parent
在父流中
interface for stream there's also a
流的接口也有一个
method called sequential as well and the
称为顺序的方法以及
Java Doc's are very vague about it but
Java Doc对此非常含糊，但是
the idea is that parallel will return a
这个想法是并行将返回一个
parallel stream or the existing stream
并行流或现有流
if it's already parallel and sequential
如果已经是并行和顺序的
will do the same for sequential ones
对于顺序的将执行相同的操作
these are both intermediate operations
这些都是中间操作
on stream meaning they produce a new
投放中意味着他们产生了新的
stream from what we're dealing with
从我们正在处理的内容中
and then it we don't get any values
然后我们没有任何价值
until we put a terminal expression on
直到我们在终端表达式上
there as we do with stream processing
就像我们处理流一样
normally if you want to find out if a
通常，如果您想找出是否
stream is sequential or parallel then
流是顺序的还是并行的，然后
there's a method called is parallel that
有一种叫做并行的方法
returns a boolean nice and simple easy
返回一个布尔值尼斯和简单容易
to find out whether you're dealing with
找出你是否正在与
a sequential one or a parallel one but
连续的一个或并行的一个，但是
in general unless it says parallel it's
一般来说，除非它说平行
sequential now one of the things that is
现在连续的事情之一是
not obvious from the API which is very
从API来看不是很明显
important to know is that you can't do
重要的是要知道你做不到
part of a pipeline sequentially and then
管道的一部分，然后
part in parallel now we'll talk about
并行部分，现在我们将讨论
which things you want to do sequentially
您想按顺序执行哪些操作
which things you want to do parallel in
您想并行执行哪些操作
a minute but the point is is that you
一分钟，但关键是你
cannot just simply change from
不能仅仅从
sequential to parallel and back and have
顺序平行并返回并具有
that change in the middle of a pipeline
管道中间的变化
now if you know how stream processing
现在，如果您知道流处理的方式
works this is not a surprise but just as
作品，这不足为奇，但正如
a quick illustration I have a class in
我在上课的快速插图
my repo called sequential two parallel
我的仓库叫连续两个平行
tests and if I go to IntelliJ here and I
测试，如果我在这里和我一起去IntelliJ
went to the yes this is the one I want
去了，这是我想要的那个
and I'm clearly gonna have to make the
而且我显然必须要做
font bigger but let me open this first
字体较大，但让我先打开
so here is sequential two parallel tests
所以这是顺序的两个并行测试
and let me mom improve the font size
让我妈妈改善字体大小
because we changed everything here so
因为我们在这里改变了一切
it'll only take me a moment let me make
我只需要一点时间就可以
it I don't know 35 or 36 how about that
我不知道35或36
is that readable you see that in the
可读性您在
back and great it didn't do it but
回来，很好，它没有做到，但是
hopefully it will
希望它将
alright I'll just do that and then I'll
好吧，我会这样做，然后我会
fix it later ok so the idea here is they
稍后再解决，所以这里的想法是
just have a series of test cases just to
只是有一系列的测试用例
illustrate the mechanism so here I say
说明机制，所以我在这里说
if I use the of method on a stream I'm
如果我在流上使用of方法
asserting that when I call dot is
断言当我叫点是
parallel that will be false
并行将是错误的
same thing on iterate is parallel as
迭代上的同一件事与
false generate with math colon colon
用数学冒号冒号生成错误
random there's my supplier specifically
随机，有我的供应商专门
a double supplier that also is not
也不是双重供应商
parallel here if I created a list of
如果我创建了一个列表
elements and then call the stream method
元素，然后调用stream方法
again that's not parallel but of course
同样，这不是平行的，但当然
obviously if I call parallel first it
显然，如果我先调用并行
will be so I change that to true and
因此，我将其更改为true，
then down here if I call parallel stream
然后在这里，如果我叫并行流
of course it's true so that's all well
当然是真的，所以一切都很好
and good that's not surprising where
很好，这并不奇怪
things get interesting is if you try to
事情变得有趣的是，如果您尝试
do parallel and then sequential
并行然后顺序
consecutively or even if you put values
连续，甚至即使您输入值
in between like here I'm saying let's go
在这之间我说我们走吧
to parallel because all I want to do is
并行，因为我想做的就是
double the elements and that's an
加倍元素，这是一个
independent associative operation that
独立的联合行动
would be fine for parallel I can even
对于平行我会很好
look at the values as they go by and
观察价值流逝并
then I want to do sorting and sorting I
然后我要进行排序和排序
want to do sequentially because that's a
想顺序执行，因为那是一个
stateful operation and it already has
状态操作，它已经
its own parallel type of mechanism
自己的并行机制
concurrent mechanism built into it I
我内置的并发机制
mean it's not a true parallel sort but
表示这不是真正的并行排序，但
it's just an existing sort so this is a
这只是一个现有的排序，所以这是一个
sort of thing you're tempted to do well
你很想做得好
it turns out that parallel and
事实证明，平行和
sequential are basically setting or
顺序基本上是设置或
unsetting a flag and since nothing
取消设置标志，因为什么也没有
happens till I hit the terminal
直到我击中终点站
expression here the collect what you
在这里表达收集你的东西
would find is that once I hit the
会发现，一旦我击中
terminal expression it will say well we
终端表达会很好
started parallel we switch to sequential
开始并行我们切换到顺序
the entire stream will be treated as a
整个流将被视为
sequential stream ok so you can't turn
顺序流好，所以您无法打开
it on for part and then turn it off
将其打开一部分然后关闭
you'd basically have to do it as two
你基本上必须做两个
separate streams there's no easy way
分开流没有简单的方法
around that okay so also if you're going
好吧，如果你要走的话
to return a stream and then call
返回流，然后调用
something you know try to put them in
你知道的东西尝试把它们放进去
separate methods again since nothing
再次分离方法，因为什么也没有
happens until you get the terminal
直到您到达终端为止
expression that's not going to help
表达不会有帮助
either you might as well do the parallel
您也可以并行进行
part return a collection with of doubles
部分返回具有双打的集合
if you will and then do the sequential
如果您愿意，然后按顺序进行
part with the sort and that's about the
与排序有关的部分
closest you can come to that so I can
最接近你可以做到的，所以我可以
just
只是
for the sake of argument I can execute
为了争辩我可以执行
this entire class and you see all the
这整个课，你会看到
tests pass and therefore all those
测试通过，因此所有这些
asserts about sequential and parallel
关于顺序和并行的断言
are true and not a big surprise so again
是真的，没有什么大的意外，所以再次
that's something you need to be aware of
这是您需要注意的
however if you're not aware of that that
但是，如果您不知道这一点
can bite you okay now when is parallel
平行的时候可以咬你好吗
worth doing here are the basic
值得在这里做的是基本
requirements first of all I mentioned
我首先提到的要求
the operations have to be independent
操作必须独立
and associative they do not have to be
和联系他们不必
commutative because it's not going to
可交换的，因为它不会
try to switch the order a times B versus
尝试将顺序切换为B与
B times a it's not going to do that what
B次a不会那样做
parallelism is all about or concurrency
并行是关于或并发的
is all about is grouping so instead of
是关于分组的全部内容，而不是
processing a hundred elements
处理一百个元素
sequentially we're going to divide them
依次地，我们将它们分开
into groups of twenty-five and process
分为二十五和过程
them in individual groups so it's all
他们在各个小组中，所以这就是全部
about the associative nature of the
关于...的关联性质
operation not the commutative nature so
操作不是可交换性
as long as the operation doesn't mind
只要不介意
how you group them that's a candidate
你如何将他们分组的候选人
for parallelism also we want it to be
对于并行性，我们也希望它是
stateless if we can I'm saying that by
如果可以的话，我是无状态的
saying independent so that the each
说独立，使每个
element doesn't depend on surrounding
元素不依赖于周围环境
elements or any other element like that
元素或类似的任何其他元素
doubling operation is clearly
加倍操作很明显
independent and clearly associative so
独立且明确的关联性
that's a minimum requirement to even
这是最低要求
bother with parallel if you're doing
如果您在做并行操作
something stateful or that has
有状态的或具有
additional dependencies it's not going
其他依赖关系没有
to get you any benefit here now another
为了给您带来任何好处
requirement is this thing you will see
要求是这件事，你会看到
expressed on various websites as n times
在各个网站上表示为n次
Q greater than 10,000 where n is
Q大于10,000，其中n是
basically the number of data elements
基本上是数据元素的数量
and Q is the amount of time spent
Q是花费的时间
processing each element now the problem
现在处理每个元素的问题
with that measurement n times Q greater
该测量结果n乘以Q
than 10,000 is they never put a unit on
超过10,000是他们从未将单位放在
Q so I don't I mean how do you measure
问，所以我不是说你如何衡量
so let's just say it this way the
所以我们这样说吧
product of n times Q must be above some
Q的n乘积必须大于某个
threshold you are introducing overhead
引入开销的阈值
by going to parallel you are basically
通过并行，您基本上
by default as we're going to see
默认情况下，因为我们将看到
introducing a fork joint pool splitting
引入叉叉池拆分
up the work and individual sections and
工作和各个部分
then joining them back together again
然后再将他们重新组合在一起
once they're done and that introduces
一旦完成，就会介绍
overhead and so therefore you either
因此，您要么
need enough data to make that overhead
需要足够的数据来增加开销
worth it
值得
or there needs to be enough time per
否则每个时间需要足够的时间
element that that overhead
那个开销的元素
worth it and things like multiplying or
是值得的，诸如乘法或
adding numbers together believe it or
相加数字相信或
not is rarely worth it the basic Java
不，基本的Java很少值得
processor is incredibly fast at
处理器速度极快
processing primitives and I'll come back
处理原语，我会回来
to that as an illustration I mean if I'm
举例来说，我的意思是
simply adding up numbers I've done many
只是加起来，我做了很多
test cases with say 10 million numbers
一千万个数字的测试用例
and that's nowhere near enough to make
而且还远远不够
it worth it to go to parallel sequential
值得去并行顺序
is so fast on that it's hardly worth
如此之快以至于几乎不值得
going parallel and I'll give you some
并行，我给你一些
better guidance about that as we go now
我们现在就此进行更好的指导
another requirement that people don't
人们不要的另一个要求
talk about that often is that the data
经常谈论的是数据
also needs to be easy to partition
还需要易于分区
remember that when we go to parallel
记得当我们去平行
streams in Java
Java流
we are using this fork/join pool under
我们在下面使用这个fork / join池
the hood we are simply dividing up the
引擎盖，我们只是分开
work into equal sized sections and doing
分成相等大小的部分并做
the processing on each section and then
每个部分的处理，然后
merging them well if the if the machine
如果机器很好地合并它们
can't figure out where the begin and
不知道从哪里开始
where the end is then it's not so easy
到底哪里不那么容易
to divide them up so if you're doing say
把它们分开，所以如果你说
an int stream with a range well that's
具有范围井的int流是
easy it knows where the start is it
很容易知道从哪里开始
knows where the end is range or range
知道终点在哪里或范围
closed but if you do a stream dot
关闭，但如果您有流点
iterate with a limit that's asking too
也要问一个限制
much it doesn't necessarily know how now
很多不一定现在知道
of course from a mechanical point of
当然从机械角度来看
view if you're dealing with an array as
查看您是否正在处理数组
the source of your data great nice
您的数据来源非常好
consecutive memory locations that's a
连续的内存位置是
dream scenario for this whereas if
梦想的场景，而如果
you're dealing with a linked list well
你正在处理一个链表
good luck ok so the idea is that the
祝你好运，所以这个想法是
datum should come from a situation that
数据应来自以下情况：
is easy to partition if and if you have
如果有的话，很容易分区
that then it's worth it you can expect
那值得你期待
to get a significant gain out of
从中获得重大收益
parallel parallelization now in order to
现在并行并行化
show a demo I'm going to show a simple
展示一个演示，我将展示一个简单的
demo that is going to just run a main
演示将只运行一个主
method and illustrate this but of course
方法并说明这一点，但当然
all demonstrations like that should be
所有这样的示威都应该
viewed with some suspicion because
有点怀疑，因为
you've got this hot start of the JVM you
您已经有了JVM的热启动
don't know what else is going on in the
不知道这是怎么回事
system etc there is a project that comes
系统等，有一个项目来了
from the open JDK project called the
来自名为的开放JDK项目
Java micro benchmark harness many of you
Java Micro基准测试利用了许多人
may have heard of it it is a it is a
可能听说过它是一个
Java project that is based on
基于的Java项目
annotations and it allows you
注释，它允许您
to run a method as many times as you
尽可能多地运行一种方法
specify it does a series of warm-up
指定它进行一系列的热身
iterations it'll create a forked JVM
迭代它将创建一个分叉的JVM
just to execute you can do all kinds of
只是执行，你可以做各种
optimizations in that and this is an
优化，这是一个
excellent way of I don't say monitor
我不说显示器的好方法
measuring basically the performance of
基本上衡量
individual methods on that so I put in a
个别的方法，所以我把
link to the the jmh project the project
链接到jmh项目
is not real well documented but they do
没有真正有据可查的，但他们确实
have lots of samples and that's helpful
有很多样本，这很有帮助
now I'm running it two different ways
现在我以两种不同的方式运行它
one is that Gradle I'd use a Gradle
一个是摇篮，我会用摇篮
build tool for everything I do
为我所做的一切构建工具
Gradle has a nice jmh plug-in and that
Gradle有一个不错的jmh插件，
works fine that's what I have in the
工作正常，这就是我所拥有的
repository if you were to take a look at
仓库，如果你要看看
the codebase alternatively IntelliJ IDEA
代码库或IntelliJ IDEA
also has a jmh plug-in that lets you
还有一个jmh插件，可让您
just run as and run as a method and it
只是作为方法运行，并且它
will do the benchmarking right there so
将在那里进行基准测试，因此
I do recommend this is a nice tool to
我建议这是一个不错的工具
give you data that you can actually have
给您您实际上可以拥有的数据
some faith in you know that might
对你的某些信念知道那可能
actually be something you could
实际上是可以做的事
reproduce now to show this again I want
现在重现以再次显示此内容
to mention when you do parallel streams
在进行并行流时要提及
you are by default delegating to a fork
您默认情况下委派给叉子
join pool now fork join pool was a class
现在加入池fork加入池是一个类
added in Java 1.7 it is an executor
Java 1.7中添加的它是执行程序
service so if you're used to using
服务，如果您习惯使用
executor service or executor snoo cached
执行器服务或执行器snoo已缓存
pool or fixed size pool or whatever this
池或固定大小的池或其他
is just another one but this is the one
只是另一个而已
they use by default it does the now the
他们默认使用它现在做
common pool which is a method inside
公共池，这是一种内部方法
fork/join pool a static method call
fork / join池的静态方法调用
common pool returns the common pool for
公共池返回用于的公共池
the JVM now this has mixed reputation
JVM现在这有好坏参半
because people go well if other things
因为如果有其他事情，人们会很顺利
are going on in the system I'm using the
在我正在使用的系统中进行
same pool and that's bad yeah you could
同一个游泳池，那是不好的，你可以
argue it but it is a highly optimized
争论它，但它是高度优化的
pool that also does what they call
他们也称呼的游泳池
work-stealing meaning that if if extra
偷工的意思是，如果额外
jobs have been submitted and one thread
作业已提交，一个线程
happens to be idle it'll go and grab the
碰巧闲着，它会去抓住
work okay so it really does have
工作正常，所以确实有
excellent performance I would say try it
我要说的是出色的性能
and if it doesn't give you the
如果没有给你
performance you want then most of the
您想要的性能然后
methods in completable future that I'm
我可以完成的未来方法
going to show allow you to specify
要显示允许您指定
an executor service or more properly a
遗嘱执行人服务或更准确地说是
cool also if you want to and I have an
如果你想也很酷，我有一个
illustration of that as well now when
现在的说明
you make a fork joint pool technically
你专门制作叉叉池
the default pool size of that is equal
的默认池大小等于
to this calculation runtime get runtime
到此计算运行时获取运行时
dot available processors actually I
点实际可用的处理器
think I meant a plus one there rather
认为我的意思是那里加一
than a minus one and I'll fix that
而不是减号，我会解决的
but here's the thing I on my laptop here
但是这是我在笔记本电脑上的东西
which I suppose these days I should call
我想这些天我应该打电话给
a private cloud server right yeah it's
是一个私有云服务器，对
just a laptop any rate this laptop is
只是一台笔记本电脑，这台笔记本电脑的价格是多少
about four years old I'm waiting for the
大约四岁，我在等
for them I still want them to release a
对于他们，我仍然希望他们释放
better Mac I'm really hoping you know
更好的Mac，我真的希望你知道
but at any rate I have a course on this
但无论如何，我对此都有一个课程
machine so when I create this common
机器，所以当我创建这个共同点时
pool and get the pool size this
池并获取池大小
calculation of runtime dot get runtime
计算运行时点获取运行时
dot available processors returns seven
点可用处理器返回七
but then you add one because the pool
但随后您添加了一个，因为该池
size may be seven but main is still
大小可能是七个，但主要仍然
operating as well so I just think of it
运作良好，所以我想到了
as the work being distributed among all
因为工作被分配给所有人
eight cores and that's really how it
八个核心，实际上就是这样
does work in practice now I'll show you
可以在实践中工作了，我会告诉你
in a bit how you could change the number
稍微改变一下数字
of threads if you want okay but first
线程数，如果您想要的话，但是首先
I'd like to demonstrate this so I have a
我想演示一下，所以我有一个
class called parallel demo let me go
叫并行演示的课让我走
back here and I'll open that one up so
回到这里，我将其打开
what I'm doing here is I have this
我在这里做的是我有这个
method that's going to double a number
将数字加倍的方法
this is a function obviously and the
这显然是一个功能，
reason I put it in a separate method is
我把它放在单独的方法中的原因是
so I could manually introduce asleep
所以我可以手动引入睡眠
inside it and I'm also going to do what
在里面，我也要去做
I normally do whenever I'm trying to do
我通常会在尝试时做
anything with parallelization which is I
任何带有并行化的东西是我
like to put in a print of the current
喜欢打印当前
threads name so that I know which thread
线程名称，以便我知道哪个线程
is operating to make sure I am using up
正在操作以确保我用光了
all the threads and things are working
所有线程和事物都在工作
now the main method here started off
现在这里的主要方法开始了
with a very small array list that has
具有非常小的数组列表
six elements and what I'm going to do
六个要素以及我要做什么
let me skip this down here I'm going to
让我跳过这里，我要
make actually I'll make this in stream
让我在流中做这个
right here and I'll start off with it
就在这里，我将从它开始
sequentially let me turn off the
按顺序让我关闭
parallel part and I'll just map it to
平行部分，我将其映射到
double it so that's going to double each
将其翻倍，以便每次翻倍
number but it's going to
数字，但它将
introduce the the sleep as well now if I
现在介绍一下睡眠
cut this down to only six elements right
减少到只有六个元素
now then I have enough cores for each
现在，我每个人都有足够的核心
core to get an element okay so my n is
核心得到一个元素好，所以我的n是
very small but I've got enough
很小但是我受够了
processors to handle them all
处理器来处理所有这些
individually that's why I had to
这就是为什么我不得不
introduce a delay otherwise I wouldn't
引入延迟，否则我不会
see any change at all from going to
从看到任何变化
parallel so I'm going to double them all
并行的，所以我要把它们全部加倍
and then sum them I actually don't care
然后总结一下，我实际上不在乎
about the Sun but I need a terminal
关于太阳，但我需要一个终端
operation in order to make the stream
操作以使流
actually work and here I'm going to use
实际工作，我将在这里使用
instant dot now in between in other
即时点现在在其他之间
words I'm just going to print out the
我将要打印出的单词
amount of time this took okay so now if
花费的时间还可以，所以现在如果
I do this sequentially I've got six
我依次执行此操作，我有六个
numbers I introduced a hundred
我介绍了一百个数字
millisecond delay well by golly that
毫秒延迟很好
ought to take about six seconds and if I
应该花大约六秒钟，如果我
look at the output here it was a little
看一下这里的输出
over 600 milliseconds I introduced a
我介绍了600多个毫秒
hundred millisecond delay on each so it
每一个都延迟一百毫秒
took a little over 600 milliseconds
花了600多毫秒
which is what I expect and then if I
这是我的期望，然后，如果我
turn in turn the parallel back on and
依次打开并行并
run it again you see first of all in the
再次运行它，您首先会看到
pools here there are the workers 1
这里有工人池1
through 5 plus main see so I still count
通过5加主要看到，所以我仍然数
that and main will be reused and this
那和主要将被重用，这
took just over a hundred milliseconds
花了一百多毫秒
now this is the dream scenario for
现在这是梦想的场景
parallelization ok if you're if you live
并行化，如果您在现场
a good life and everything works out
美好的生活，一切顺利
this is what you'll get you know that's
这就是您将要知道的
not going to happen very often but it
不会经常发生，但是它
can be very beneficial this is the one
可能非常有益，这是一个
you show your manager you know in order
你向你的经理展示你知道的顺序
to get them to let you go ahead and work
让他们让你继续工作
on this you know so now but the thing is
关于这一点，你现在就知道了，但问题是
is I just did what I said not to do
我只是做了我说过的不做的事情
right I rent something in a main method
对，我用主要方法租东西
just to demonstrate this was working
只是为了证明这是可行的
well with that in mind I also have this
考虑到这一点，我也有这个
doubling demo in a jmh package and here
将jmh包中的演示翻倍
you can see this is using annotations
您可以看到这是使用注释
that come from jmh I'm looking for the
来自jmh的我正在寻找
average times I want the time unit to be
我希望时间单位是
milliseconds everything is scoped to a
毫秒范围内
single thread each calculation I'm doing
我正在执行的每个计算都使用单线程
to fork JVMs I tried to set the memory
派生我试图设置内存的JVM
to be as big as I could afford so that
尽可能地大
memory was not an issue in this
内存不是这个问题
calculation and then there's my same
计算，然后有我的相同
double it but this
加倍，但这
time I put in the two methods here one
一次我在这里输入两种方法
with sequential one with parallel and I
与顺序并行与我
added the benchmark annotation on top of
在的顶部添加了基准注释
them now I could run it but it would
他们现在我可以运行它，但它将
take a while to run now because it would
花点时间运行，因为它会
do 20 warm-up iterations and then 20
做20次热身迭代，然后进行20次
actual iterations which it would average
平均的实际迭代
and it would do this twice for each of
并且会对每个
them so I would have all of those runs
他们，所以我将所有这些运行
and with my delays that would take a
加上我的拖延，
while so instead what I've done is I've
而相反，我要做的是
copied the results and just put them
复制结果并将其放入
here so here is the sequential one and
这是顺序的，
what you could see is the average over
您可以看到的是
the 40 was just over 600 milliseconds
40刚好超过600毫秒
per operation and with parallel it was
每次操作并并行
just over a hundred milliseconds per
每百毫秒
operation and those values I believe
操作和我相信的那些价值观
okay so it's a very nice tool and it
好吧，这是一个非常好的工具，
does give you confidence in in the
确实让您对
calculations that you're doing so that's
您正在执行的计算是
really all you need to know to get
真的，您需要了解的所有信息
started with the parallel stream stuff
从并行流的东西开始
and I wanted to give you that background
我想给你那个背景
now one other thing that people always
现在人们总是一回事
ask is how do you change the number of
问问你如何改变数量
threads okay there is and this is listed
线程有没有，这已列出
in the Java Docs themselves if you go
在Java Docs本身中
into the Java Doc's for fork/join pool
进入Java文档的fork / join池
there is a setting called Believe It or
有一个设置叫做“相信它”或
Not Java dot util dot concurrent dot
不是Java点util点并发点
fork/join pool command dot parallelism
fork / join池命令点并行
that mouthful and you can set that in
那满口的，你可以把它放在
your on the command line with a dash
您在命令行上用破折号
capital D flag or you can just do system
大写D标志或您可以做系统
dot set property and pick another number
点设置属性并选择另一个数字
and I've actually done a calculation
我实际上已经做了一个计算
like that as well this one called common
也像这样
pool size just to show you what I mean
游泳池的大小只是为了告诉你我的意思
so here this one I just tried making a
所以在这里我只是试着做一个
range from one to three million and some
从一百万到三百万不等
of them in parallel and then I could
他们并行，然后我可以
print out the pool size and then I could
打印出池的大小，然后我可以
say oh I could make a manual one
说哦，我可以做一个手工
whatever size I want and then I could
无论我想要什么尺寸，然后我都可以
use the regular old submit method which
使用常规的旧提交方法
is going to return on a fork joint task
将要返回叉叉任务
which means eventually I'll have to call
这意味着最终我将不得不打电话
get and that throws all these exceptions
得到并抛出所有这些异常
we'll get to that in a minute but this
我们会在一分钟内解决这个问题
is the base without changing the
是不改变基础的基础
defaults all I would have to do is
默认我要做的就是
change the system dot get property and
更改系统点获取属性并
set this value and I could run it in
设置这个值，我可以运行它
parallel as well now if you change the
现在，如果您更改
size
尺寸
of the pool too much bigger than the
游泳池的面积比
number of processors on your disk you're
您磁盘上的处理器数量
not likely to see a whole lot of
不太可能看到很多
improvement okay again the common pool
改善还可以，公共游泳池
is choosing processors based or the
选择基于处理器还是
thread pool based on the number of
基于线程池的数量
processors you have that's a pretty good
您拥有的处理器非常不错
guess you know but you do have the
猜猜你知道，但是你确实有
mechanism should you wish to do it
您应该这样做的机制
it is available and certainly worth
它是可用的，当然值得
experimenting with if you like okay so
如果可以的话尝试一下
enough with that one
足够那个
now what was added in Java 8 was was
现在在Java 8中添加的是
completed but that's based on future the
已完成，但这是基于未来的
future interface was added in Java 1.5
Java 1.5中添加了将来的接口
ok this has been in there since the
好的，自从
addition of the Java dot util dot
Java点util点的添加
concurrent package and the thing about
并发包和关于
the future interface is that when you
未来的界面是，当您
return a future using the submit method
使用Submit方法返回未来
takes a callable on an executor service
接受执行人服务
then the method returns immediately and
然后该方法立即返回
then you could go about doing other
那你可以去做其他的
calculations the problem with future
计算未来的问题
well one issue with future is that in
未来的一个问题是
order to get the value out of the future
为了从未来获得价值
you have to call get and get as a
您必须致电get and get as
blocking call so eventually you got a
阻止通话，所以最终您得到了
call get and hope that you're done or
打电话给get，希望你完成了，或者
that you're ready to wait for it to be
你准备好等待它成为
finished now that's ok but that's the
现在完成就可以了，但是那是
fact of life where life becomes
生活成为生活的事实
difficult is that if I want to have
困难的是，如果我想拥有
multiple futures if I want to say first
如果要先说多个期货
do this then do that then do the other
做这个然后做那个然后做另一个
now I got a problem because now I'm in
现在我有一个问题，因为现在我在
what they call call back hell or I've
他们叫回地狱或我已经
got some other way where I have to wait
还有其他方法我必须等待
for everything to beacon finished and
信标完成的一切，
now I feel like I'm back to blocking
现在我觉得我要回到封锁
again this is where completable future
再次，这是可以完成的未来
comes in completable future makes it
在可完成的未来中实现
very easy to coordinate multiple tasks
非常容易协调多个任务
so that it waits for one to be finished
这样它就等待一个完成
before the next execute and so on so one
在下一次执行之前，依此类推
way people have tried in the past to
人们过去尝试过的方式
coordinate regular old futures is that
协调常规的旧期货是
the future has a method called is done
未来有一种方法叫做完成
and you could do this thing called busy
你可以做这个忙的事情
waiting put in a while loop that just
等待放一个while循环
keeps asking are you done are you done
一直问你做完了吗
are we there yet are we there yet are we
我们在那儿吗我们在那儿吗
there yet and it's exactly that annoying
在那里，那真是烦人
ok and the problem is is that that can
好的，问题是那可以
generate literally billions of calls you
产生数十亿个电话
know especially given how fast
知道特别快
processors are right now
处理器是现在
so while this works and I have a demo of
所以虽然这可行，我有一个演示
it I don't necessarily recommend it okay
我不一定推荐它
this is really a pain and this again is
这真的很痛苦，这又是
partly why the the completable future
部分原因是可完成的未来
was created and I'm going to jump to
被创建了，我要跳到
that now so completable future is a
现在如此可完成的未来是
class that's all about coordination it
所有关于协调的课程
implements two interfaces future and
实现将来的两个接口
completion stage and that means there's
完成阶段，这意味着
a lot of methods involved and I want to
涉及很多方法，我想
show you the basic idea the first thing
向您展示基本思想
is though is how do you complete a
虽然是如何完成一个
completable future if I don't want to
如果我不想完成的未来
call get which or which I could if I
打电话给我，如果我可以
just want to complete it there are three
只是想完成它，有三个
built-in ways there's complete which
内置方式可以完成
takes a value completed future or even
取得价值，甚至是未来
complete exceptionally now before I go
我走之前现在特别完成
to the code here let me give you an idea
这里的代码让我给你一个想法
how they're used together so here's the
它们如何一起使用，所以这是
idea say I have some cash a map of
想法说我有一些现金
integer to product I use the concurrent
我使用并发的产品的整数
hash map here so a cache of integer to
哈希映射在这里，所以整数的缓存
product and now I have a method called
产品，现在我有一个方法叫做
get local which is going to take the ID
获取将要使用ID的本地
here and pull out the value from the
在这里从中取出价值
cache but I also have this legacy code
缓存，但我也有这个旧代码
that came from somewhere else that has a
来自其他地方的
get remote method takes an ID I'm
获取远程方法需要一个ID
introducing my simulation of a network
介绍我对网络的仿真
delay if you will or the legacy delay
如果您愿意，请延迟，否则将延迟
then I also have the situation where it
那我也有这样的情况
could throw an exception if something
可能会引发异常
went wrong I needed it to be predictable
出错了，我需要它是可预测的
so I could you liked my choice of ID
所以我可以喜欢我选择的ID
there yes no I'm not going to make any
是的，不，我不会做任何事情
jokes moving on so I wanted something
开玩笑，所以我想要一些东西
predictable so I could write a test case
可预测的，所以我可以写一个测试用例
for it so I picked an ID and down here
为此，我选择了一个ID，然后在这里
I'm ultimately going to return the value
我最终将返回价值
now this is being done sequentially
现在这是按顺序完成的
actually let's see how these are used so
让我们看看如何使用它们
if I have the get local and the get
如果我有本地和获得
remote and these are private methods
远程，这些是私有方法
then the public method is called get
然后将公共方法称为get
product with an ID now in normal Java
现在具有普通Java ID的产品
code that was not concurrent you'd write
您不会编写的并发代码
get I get product with an ID you'd
得到我带有您想要的ID的产品
return a product in this case I want to
在这种情况下，我要退货
return a completable future of the
返回一个可完成的未来
product so this will return immediately
产品，因此将立即返回
so you try the local one and when you
所以你尝试本地的，当你
call get on a map and there's it's not
打电话到地图上，那里不是
in there you get back a null so I'll say
在那儿你得到一个空值，所以我会说
look if it's not null if it worked
看它是否不为null是否有效
then I use completed future and say yep
然后我用完整的未来说
there's my product
有我的产品
the futures done we're ready to go if it
期货完成了，我们准备好了
fails if it's not in the cache basically
如果基本上不在缓存中，将失败
now I have to use my legacy system so
现在我必须使用我的旧系统
I'll make a completable future here I'll
我将在这里创造一个美好的未来
call get remote returns a product
致电获取远程退回产品
eventually put it in the cache and this
最终将其放入缓存中
time I call complete on the already
我已经完成的通话时间
instantiated completable future and
实例化的可完成的未来和
return that finally if something goes
最后，如果有事情返回
horribly wrong in all of this I catch an
在所有这一切中，我都非常错误
exception make a completable future and
创造一个可完成的未来
call complete exceptionally which wraps
调用异常完成
the exception itself so that I can check
异常本身，以便我可以检查
the exception that comes out and I could
出现的异常，我可以
check its source and find out what
检查其来源并找出原因
happened with it and all of that works
它发生了，所有的工作
as well so that's why you have all three
这就是为什么这三个原因
different methods this is a nice
不同的方法，这是一个不错的选择
illustration of that working given our
鉴于我们的工作说明
time restrictions I'm going to just say
时间限制我只想说
that take my word for it that this works
我相信这是可行的
and I'm gonna go on to another example
我将继续另一个例子
okay now what about running
好吧，现在跑步
asynchronously because all of that was
异步，因为所有这些都是
synchronous except for the fact that the
同步，除了
product the method returned right away
产品立即返回的方法
okay well completable future implements
可以很好地完成的未来工具
both future that's why you have a get
都是未来，这就是为什么你拥有
method and the others join etc it also
方法和其他人加入等
implements completion stage which has
实施完成阶段
about 38 methods in it I went and and
我去了大约38种方法
counted which means completable future
计算意味着未来的发展
as over 50 and it looks pretty
超过50，看起来很漂亮
overwhelming fortunately there are
幸运的是，这里有
patterns we could follow the patterns
模式，我们可以遵循模式
look like this the methods that have the
看起来像这样的方法
word apply in them like apply apply well
单词适用于他们，就像适用得很好
we'll see it apply take as an argument a
我们将看到它适用作为一个参数
function because the mnemonic is
功能，因为助记符是
remember if you looked at the function
记得你看过这个功能
interface inside as an apply method okay
界面内部作为应用方法还可以
so this connects a function apply two
所以这连接功能适用两个
function methods that have the word
具有单词的功能方法
accept on them take a consumer again
再次接受消费者
inside the consumer interface your
在使用者介面内
single abstract method is accept so it's
单个抽象方法被接受，因此
trying to make it easier to remember
试图使其更容易记住
that the run methods take a runnable
运行方法需要一个可运行的
that's easy the supply methods take a
这很容易，供应方法需要
supplier so when you see these method
供应商，所以当您看到这些方法时
names you can just identify from those
您可以从中识别出的名称
categories right away which of these
马上分类
they fit in
他们适合
now there's methods like then and this
现在有那样的方法
is how you wind up chaining them
是如何结束它们的链接
together so see there's the apply so
在一起所以看到有适用
apply takes a function I'm going to take
apply需要一个我要使用的功能
each element and I'm going to square it
每个元素，我要平方它
say this example by the way is right out
说这个例子是正确的
of the Java Docs I didn't even run this
我甚至没有运行过Java文档
this is right out of the Java Docs and
这就是Java文档
then except takes a consumer at which
然后除了带一个消费者
point I'm going to print it see I just
点，我要打印它，看看我只是
use a method reference but so be it and
使用方法参考，但事实并非如此
then run and this takes a runnable which
然后运行，这需要一个可运行的
is for who knows why printing a carriage
适用于谁知道为什么要打印马车
return okay but that's the idea by using
返回好吧，但这是通过使用
these then methods then each method will
这些方法然后每个方法将
wait for the future to be done before
等待未来完成
going to the next one automatically now
现在自动转到下一个
they can run asynchronously but it's
他们可以异步运行，但是
sort of like joining on threads one is
有点像加入线程
waiting for the completion of the
等待完成
previous before it moves on each way and
之前，它在每个方向上前进，并且
by chaining together methods like this
通过像这样链接方法
you can accomplish much more complex
您可以完成更复杂的工作
tasks so you saw then there's also some
任务，所以您看到了还有一些
patterns in the method names like either
方法名称中的模式
which says either this one or that one
说这一个或那个
whichever finishes first there's both
以先完成者为准
waiting for both there's combined which
等待两者结合在一起
says wait for this one and then provide
说等待这个然后提供
a by function that's going to take the
一个按功能，将采取
result of the first one and a
第一个结果和一个
completable future and put them together
可完成的未来，并将它们放在一起
so it's going to wind up allowing you to
所以它即将结束，您可以
combine results and again I'll show you
结合结果，我再告诉你
an example so the other pattern that
一个例子，另一个模式
comes is that in many of the methods
就是在许多方法中
they end with the word async and then
他们以异步这个词结尾，然后
there's overloads that don't the ones
有没有的超载
that don't operate in the same thread as
不能与
the caller so back here
来电者回到这里
none of these say async on them this is
这些都没有对他们说异步
delegating to a thread in the pork joint
委托给猪肉接头中的一根线
pool but all three of these methods are
池，但是所有这三种方法都是
running in the same thread altogether
完全在同一线程中运行
whereas if I used then except a sink or
而如果我用过，那么除了水槽或
then run async then it would take the
然后运行异步，那么它将需要
job and resubmit it to the fork joint
工作，然后将其重新提交到分叉
pool to go for the next one this can be
游泳池可以去下一个
very useful but again it introduces
非常有用，但再次介绍
overhead so it's something you kind of
开销，所以有点像
have to experiment with it may not
不得不尝试它可能不会
necessarily help depending on all those
一定会帮助所有这些
other factors we talked about but the
我们讨论过的其他因素，但
key is to know which one is which that
关键是要知道哪个是那个
the ones with async do operate in a
具有异步功能的人确实会在
separate thread potentially because it's
单独的线程可能是因为
resubmitting to the pool and the ones
重新提交到池和那些
without it don't so let's look at some
没有它，所以让我们来看一些
of this stuff again complete all finally
这些东西再次全部完成
there's one other category of methods in
还有另一类方法
there these are overloads
那里有超载
all the pretty much all the methods to
所有几乎所有的方法
submit jobs take an extra argument of
提交工作需要额外的论点
type executor and that would say if I
键入执行程序，那会说如果我
don't want to use the common fork/join
不想使用普通的fork / join
pool then I provide my own executor from
然后我提供我自己的执行者
the executor service okay so if you want
遗嘱执行人服务好，所以如果你想
to just use the common fork/join pool
只使用公共fork / join池
you use the overload without that
你用过载没有
otherwise you use it with it and I have
否则你用它，我有
a whole set of test cases here on
一整套的测试用例
completable future tests for example
例如可完成的未来测试
that will show for example here you
例如将在这里显示您
could see I've made a fix thread pool
可以看到我做了一个修复线程池
and I did supply a sink see that's going
我确实提供了一个水槽
to take a supplier but it's going to
采取一个供应商，但它将
submit separately to the pool and I
分别提交给我
provided the third argument with or the
为第三个参数提供或
second argument with the pool itself but
与池本身的第二个参数，但
then apply then apply then except that's
然后申请，然后申请，然后除了
all going to run in the same thread as
所有将在与同一线程中运行
the one I used in the pool that's the
我在游泳池中使用的那个
sort of idea of what you can do all
你可以做什么的想法
right now if I go back to that get
现在，如果我回到那个
product one the one that I showed before
产品一，我以前展示过的
I had everything in the remote lookup
我在远程查找中拥有了所有内容
happening sequentially legacy system it
顺序发生遗留系统
would be easy enough to replace that
将很容易替换它
part with supply async so I turn this
与供应异步的一部分，所以我把这个
into a supplier where I call get remote
进入我称之为远程的供应商
put and everything that's all done as
放，一切都完成了
part of a completable future operating
未来可完成经营的一部分
asynchronously and when that's done then
异步，然后完成
the rest will happen so that's a very
其余的会发生，所以这是一个非常
simple change that could be made to
可以进行的简单更改
hopefully improve the performance of
希望能改善
this system in general okay now we still
这个系统一般好吧，现在我们仍然
have a get method we still have a join
有一个get方法，我们还有一个联接
method it's interesting this some of the
方法有趣的是
decisions made at the beginning of Java
Java初期做出的决定
that we're still paying for one of which
我们仍在为其中之一付费
is checked exceptions right we still
被检查的异常对吧，我们仍然
have to deal with those and if you write
必须处理那些，如果你写
a lot of streaming code you deal with
您处理的许多流式代码
that all the time
一直
well the get method declares that it can
好的get方法声明它可以
throw both execution exception and
同时抛出执行异常和
interrupted exception and those require
中断的异常以及那些需要
those are checked exceptions they
这些是检查异常
require a try-catch block or throws
需要try-catch块或抛出
clause or something there's also a join
子句或其他东西也有联接
method that does the same exact thing
完全相同的方法
and the only thing it throws is a
它唯一抛出的是
completion exception which is unchecked
未检查的完成异常
so if you want to put in the try catch
因此，如果您想放入尝试
block you can put in get and if you
块，您可以放入get，如果您
don't you put in join and it's basically
你不加入加入，基本上
the same thing now of course if you
当然，如果您现在也做同样的事情
don't catch the exception down you go
不要把异常抛在脑后
you know
你懂
fine but if you want to manage it you
很好，但是如果您想管理它
call get otherwise you call join but
呼叫获取，否则您呼叫加入，但是
just like in future those methods block
就像将来那些方法阻塞一样
to wait until things are done on the
等到事情完成
other hand this is another one that
另一方面，这是另一种
people don't tend to see very often you
人们不会经常看到你
can wait for the pool to become quote
可以等待池报价
quiescent there's a word for you
静止有一个词适合你
there is a method on fork/join pool so
在fork / join池上有一个方法
here I'm getting the common pool called
在这里，我将公用池称为
a wait quiescence and it takes a time
等待静止，需要一段时间
unit and our time an integer and then a
单位和我们的时间是整数，然后是
time unit to say how long to wait for
表示要等待多长时间的时间单位
the pool to settle down and be no longer
游泳池安顿下来，不再
busy and what you can do is that if see
忙，你能做的是，如果看到
here's the concept I should say it this
这是我应该说的概念
way when you say supply async or any of
当您说供应异步或任何
those methods you have started the
您已经开始的那些方法
process you don't have to then you don't
过程中，您不必然后就不需要
have to do a start meth or anything like
必须做一个开始方法或类似的事情
that it's automatically running but the
它会自动运行，但是
common fork/join pool is composed of
普通的分叉/连接池由
demon threads so that if nothing is
恶魔线程，所以如果什么都不是
running they all get terminated see if
运行它们都被终止，看看是否
nothing else is operating it just shuts
没有其他操作，只是关闭
down so if you have a main method that
所以如果你有一个主要方法
just calls it then it the main method
只是调用它然后它是main方法
completes then you get no results
完成则没有任何结果
because all the demon threads were
因为所有的恶魔线程都是
terminated you can either call get at
终止，您可以致电获取
which point it will block and wait for
它将阻止并等待哪一点
the thing to finish or you could simply
要完成的事情，或者您可以简单地
change the timeout on the common pool
更改公共池上的超时
doing away quiescence and make it long
消除静态并使之变长
enough that it will not finish before
足够它不会完成之前
your calculation finishes and either one
您的计算完成，并且其中一个
of these work the actual concept is that
这些工作的实际概念是
in a real system where you're submitting
在您要提交的真实系统中
jobs all the time the pool doesn't go
泳池一直都在工作
quiescent you don't have that problem
静止不存在问题
but this is one of those ones that until
但这是直到
you see it you may not even recognize
你看到它，你甚至可能不认识
it's there and it's very useful in those
它在那里，在那些地方非常有用
simple cases where the pool would have
池将具有的简单情况
gone away and you wonder you're looking
走了，你想知道你在找
at somebody's code you're caught why
在某人的密码下，您被抓住了
didn't they call get why didn't they
他们没有打电话给他们为什么不
call what happened here how did it
打电话说这里发生了什么
complete it completed anyway just
完成它反正只是完成了
because they waited ok one other thing I
因为他们等了我一件事
want to point out before I show you the
在我告诉你之前要指出
bigger example there are many methods in
更大的例子中有很多方法
that completable future class one of
该可完成的未来课程之一
them is called all of it takes a var arg
他们被称为所有需要一个可变参数
list of completable futures of any kind
任何种类的可完成期货清单
it's a static method the problem with
这是一个静态方法的问题
this method
这种方法
is it returns completable future up type
它返回可完成的未来向上类型
void now that would be fine if I don't
现在无效，如果我不这样做会很好
care about the results out of any of
不在乎任何结果
these guys if I do care about the
这些家伙，如果我真的在乎
results the question is how do I get
结果问题是我怎么得到
them the simplest thing to do is to make
他们最简单的方法是
this completable future var Arg list
此可完成的未来var Arg列表
make it a separate collection and then
将其分开收集，然后
transform it into an array so that you
将其转换为数组，以便您
can call this and then call join on the
可以呼叫这个，然后在
all of so now you know they're all done
所有这些，现在您知道他们已经完成了
then you can do stream processing to
然后您可以进行流处理
extract the results and it looks
提取结果，看起来
basically like this so here is all of
基本上像这样，这就是全部
demo here so down let's look here this
演示在这里，让我们来看看这里
here's what I want to call is get value
这就是我要称呼的就是获得价值
I wanted to return an integer but I wrap
我想返回一个整数，但我换行了
it in a completable future but again if
它在可完成的未来，但如果
I'm going to do something with a sleep
我要睡觉了
in it which is how I'm going to make
在其中，这就是我要做的
this take some time that throws an
这需要一些时间，
exception it's really awkward embedding
例外，这确实很尴尬
exception handling code in a pipeline so
管道中的异常处理代码
I made it in a separate method here to
我在这里用另一种方法制作的
sleep for a random period about 100
随机睡眠约100
milliseconds or left less return 42 I
毫秒或少返回42 I
don't actually care about the value and
实际上并不在乎价值，
then here I'm going to call this a
然后在这里我将其称为
number of times and here's my demo is
次数，这是我的演示是
that I'm going to generate calling that
我将生成调用该
get value a stream of 10 completable
获得价值10个可完成流
futures and convert them to an array so
期货并将其转换为数组，以便
this is normal stream processing code
这是正常的流处理代码
using some methods you may not use very
使用某些方法，您可能不会使用
often like generate or to array which is
通常喜欢生成或数组是
really convenient
真的很方便
there's my array constructor reference
有我的数组构造函数参考
you know kind of neat that'll create an
你知道那种会创造一个
array so now I've got an array of
数组，所以现在我有一个数组
completable futures I can use that in
可完成的期货，我可以在
all of because an array matches the VAR
所有这些都是因为数组与VAR相匹配
arg argument and call join and now
arg参数并调用join和now
they're done and I can turn them back
他们完成了，我可以回头
into a stream and map them using the
到流中并使用
join method not to wait until they're
加入方法不要等到他们
finish but to get the values out of them
完成但要从中获取价值
so by calling map with the join now I've
所以现在通过联接调用map
turned my transform my stream of
把我的转变变成了
completable futures into a stream of
可完成的期货变成了
whatever the values are coming out of
无论价值来自何方
the completable futures themselves and
可完成的期货本身以及
then I could print them one by one so in
然后我可以一张一张地打印出来
this case I'll just you get a bunch of
这种情况下，我只会给你一堆
42s and I do you know so this is a nice
42岁，我知道吗，这很好
little mechanism that can be used to
可以用来的小机制
extract values out of the collection
从集合中提取值
like that now I have a
这样我现在有一个
bigger example I'm mostly just going to
更大的例子，我主要只是去
have to show it to you but this is the
必须向您展示，但这是
the idea here is that Major League
这里的想法是大联盟
Baseball provides their box scores
棒球提供他们的得分
online for free I think their own tools
免费在线我认为自己的工具
actually use these and these box scores
实际使用这些和这些盒子分数
are updated continuously now you don't
不断更新，现在您不需要
need to know anything about baseball to
需要了解棒球知识
understand this you just need to know
了解这一点，您只需要知道
there are two teams and they keep
有两个团队，他们保持
playing until there's a winner and these
玩直到有赢家，这些
the the statistics are compiled in
统计数据汇总在
something called a box score that's all
所谓的盒子分数就是全部
we need in this particular case oh and
在这种情况下，我们需要
that you don't know if a game's gonna be
你不知道游戏是否会
played until it's actually played
播放直到它实际播放
because it might get rained out okay
因为可能会下雨好
that's enough now
现在就足够了
here for example is that webpage that I
例如，这是我的网页
was mentioning MLB here and if I drill
在这里提到美国职业棒球大联盟，如果我钻
down into the current year so here's
直到今年
2017 and then there's organized by month
2017年，然后按月组织
I'll pick May 5th it's my son's birthday
我选5月5日是我儿子的生日
you know and these are the games played
你知道，这些是玩过的游戏
that day you could see them with a year
那天你可以看到他们一年
month day and then away team and home
一个月的一天，然后离开团队和主场
team and the one or two would mean first
团队和一个或两个意味着第一
or second gave a double-header any rate
或秒给双头任何速率
these are the games were actually played
这些是实际玩过的游戏
and if you look inside one of these
如果你看其中一个
you'll see there is a a file look he
你会看到有一个文件看起来他
right here called box score Jason and
就在这里被称为盒式得分的杰森和
this is the one that has all the
这是拥有所有
information in it the who's playing what
其中的信息谁在玩什么
the scores are what the results are
分数就是结果
everything so this is a system that's
一切，所以这是一个系统
been around for a long time might what I
待了很久我可能会
wanted to do in my application was
想在我的申请中做的是
access that site for a range of dates
访问该网站的日期范围
and then figure out the game links for
然后找出游戏连结
each of those dates now to do that to do
现在每个日期都要做
the networking I'm going to use okay
我要使用的网络
HTTP nice very popular networking client
HTTP非常受欢迎的网络客户端
download the JSON box scores for each
下载每个的JSON盒分数
game and I'm using the the parser for
游戏，我正在使用解析器
HTTP the I forget the name of it right
HTTP我忘了它的名字吧
now but it's a very common HTTP par so
现在，但这是一个非常常见的HTTP标准
you'll see when I see the code I'm going
当我看到要执行的代码时，您会看到
to transform each JSON object into Java
将每个JSON对象转换为Java
objects using JSON use Google's JSON so
使用JSON的对象使用Google的JSON，因此
I wrote out the classes to map that and
我写了类来映射
then see that this is all stuff that I'd
然后看到这就是我想要的所有东西
like to happen in one thread except I'd
喜欢发生在一个线程中，除了我会
like to have it concurrently for all the
喜欢同时为所有
games or as many of the games like
游戏或许多类似的游戏
could over the range once I have the
一旦我有可能会超出范围
data however I have several things I'd
数据但是我有几件事
like to do essentially simultaneously I
我喜欢同时做
would like to save the results to files
想要将结果保存到文件
that's an IO one that's going to be
这将是一个IO
slower than everything else I'd like to
比我想要的一切都要慢
just determine the score of each game
只需确定每个游戏的得分
I'd like to figure out which game had
我想弄清楚哪个游戏玩过
the highest total score and I'd like to
总分最高，我想
write them to the console with all the
将它们全部写入控制台
games scores with the max game in the
游戏得分最高的游戏
max score and all of this is in that
最大分数，所有这些都在于
other repo selling you about so here's
其他回购向您出售，所以这里是
the basic idea
基本思想
this is in that separate repository let
这是在单独的存储库中
me make this bigger and I have this get
我把这个变大，我得到这个
games here and the idea is in my method
游戏在这里，这个主意是我的方法
print games I make a completable future
纸质游戏，我创造了美好的未来
with a supply async to get the game
与供应异步获取游戏
links so I wrote my own supplier and
链接，所以我写了我自己的供应商，
this is something you don't see all the
这是你看不到的所有东西
time is you actually make a class that
时间是你实际上要上一堂课
implements at the supplier interface I
在供应商接口I上实施
don't want to do soluz a lambda for this
不想为此做一个lambda
I'm going to put in some state there's
我要进入某种状态
the base location
基本位置
there's my local date and the number of
有我的当地日期和
days I'm going to do three days by the
天，我要去做三天
way Jabba 9 makes this easier because
Jabba 9使得此操作更容易的原因是
you can actually use local dates in a
您实际上可以在
range now whereas you couldn't in Java 8
现在范围，而您不能使用Java 8
here is my actually this is the
这实际上是我的
calculation well let me start down here
计算很好，让我从这里开始
again get is going to iterate over the
再次得到将要遍历
dates for that many days and for each
每一天的日期
date get the links on that page and then
日期获取该页面上的链接，然后
if I get an empty list I'll put in an
如果我有一个空列表，我会把
empty stream otherwise I'll put in a
空流，否则我将放入
list of streams and that's why I'm using
流列表，这就是为什么我使用
flat map and that will give me overall a
平面图，这将使我整体上
list of our stream of game lengths so I
我们的游戏时长列表，所以我
collect them into a list and this is all
将它们收集到列表中，这就是全部
using LJ soup that's why I couldn't
用LJ汤，这就是为什么我不能
think of so this is all using J soup and
想到这就是全部用J汤
ok HTTP to go find those links and then
好的HTTP去找到那些链接，然后
process them ok that's step one then the
好吧，这是第一步，然后
next thing is I want to retrieve the box
接下来的事情是我想找回盒子
scores so sorry that was here
分数很抱歉那是在这里
so supply async and then apply this box
因此提供异步，然后应用此框
score Retriever and this guy is going to
得分猎犬，这个家伙要
again implement function and use
再次实现功能并使用
Google's jisan with the client so this
Google与客户的关系
down here it's probably easier to see it
在这里，可能更容易看到它
here in parallel because why not I'll
在这里并行，因为为什么不
map each of those
映射每个
links to the link to get the actual box
链接到获取实际盒子的链接
score now here's where the the
现在得分，这是
interesting part happens or one
有趣的部分发生或一个
interesting part 900 ml over but I'll
有趣的部分900毫升，但我会
finish it pretty quickly the idea now is
很快完成它的想法现在是
that I could get a rainout and if what
我可以放雨了，如果
if that happens there's no box score and
如果发生这种情况，则没有盒子得分，
there's no way to know that so I'm going
没有办法知道，所以我要去
to filter them by optional dot is
用可选点过滤它们是
present in this game pattern to result
存在于该游戏模式中以产生
mechanism I'm returning an optional if
我返回一个可选的机制
there's a rainout C so if there's a
有一个降雨C，所以如果有一个
rainout then if the box where is not
如果没有的话，请放雨
found I'll return an empty otherwise I
发现我会返回一个空的否则我
do have nullable and I get them back and
确实有可为空的东西，我让他们回来了，
then call get and then turn them into
然后打电话给get，然后把它们变成
the list here and the others are simpler
这里的列表和其他的比较简单
the others here I want to save the
其他人我要保存
result list which is simply a method up
结果列表，这只是一种方法
here to for each one save the results
在这里为每个保存结果
will file and I'm writing out how to use
将归档，我正在写出如何使用
jisan to do that and then the there's
吉桑这样做，然后有
exceptionally if something goes wrong
如果出问题了
and here's the one to get the max score
这是获得最高分的人
and get the future and all that stuff
并获得未来以及所有这些东西
and it's all in here I join them all and
一切都在这里，我和他们一起加入
then print them out and if I execute
然后将它们打印出来，如果我执行
this here let me run this execution here
这个在这里让我在这里运行这个执行
and you'll see that they will all if our
而且您会发现，如果我们
Wi-Fi holds up pop out here and I pick
Wi-Fi在这里弹出，我选择
the game with a rainout so that one
一场有一场大雨的比赛
doesn't exist and the rest of them do
不存在，其余的
and there you go there's there's
你去那里那里有
everything being calculated so again
一切都在重新计算
this is all in the code in the
这就是代码中的全部
repository so to summarize going
仓库，以便总结
parallel is easy using completable
并行很容易使用completable
futures is easy getting benefit out of
期货很容易从中获利
it is where the where your time will
这是你的时间会在哪里
actually be spent
实际花费
parallel streams delegate to the common
并行流委托给公共
fork/join pool but you could change the
fork / join池，但是您可以更改
size of that pool completable future
该库的可完成未来规模
lets you coordinate multiple ones and
让您协调多个
there are many many methods available to
有很多可用的方法
do the coordination i'll hang out if you
做协调，如果你，我会出去玩
have any questions but otherwise thank
有任何疑问，否则谢谢
you very much for coming
你非常来
you
您